<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Vee&apos;s Domain</title><description>Blog</description><link>https://veesdomain.xyz/</link><language>en</language><item><title>The college housing debacle</title><link>https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/3-27-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/3-27-2025/</guid><description>Choosing a room assignment for our housing next year sounds like a simple task, right? Well, you&apos;d be wrong. Our opportunity to choose was sweeped out right from under us.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Last month, the time for our Sophomore Housing Selection came up. The usual process for housing selection goes as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sign the housing agreement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Form a roommate/suitemate group (unless you want to be assigned randoms)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Receive info through email (your housing selection time slot, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select your room assignment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We expected the selection for Sophomore year to go smoothly because nothing suggested otherwise; choosing our housing for freshman year went super smoothly. We formed a group and signed the agreement without issue, and were fully prepared to lock in on the time we were assigned to snatch a perfect room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything fell apart when the day preceding our timeslots came, though. Midway through the first day of housing selection, we got this unexpected email stating how housing selection had closed. At first, I thought this was maybe just referring to &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; day and it would reopen at the proper times the following days. However, upon further examination, this email was essentially stating selection for the rest of the period had been closed. Me and my roommates got seriously confused, so me and another went down to the housing office to inquire about this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://files.catbox.moe/i2r345.png&quot; alt=&quot;The unexpected email housing sent us.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had to send another email to the housing office stating everyone in our group, our preferred roommate pairs, and preferred residence halls. As of writing this, they have been sending us bi-weekly emails on the status of housing, but so far we have not received any resolutions in terms of housing assignment. The whole situation is still kind of in flux.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is really irritating because it&apos;s introducing unneeded stress. Instead of housing being this smooth process, we&apos;re now uncertain of everything. We have no clue what hall we&apos;ll be placed in, and we have no clue how well they will keep our group of 6 together if at all. All of us have bonded so well together and were excited to live together again, but now that&apos;s basically foiled. I&apos;m also freaking out about the prospect of being placed with randoms; I&apos;m paranoid I would just happen to be paired with frat boys or the few other &lt;em&gt;interesting&lt;/em&gt; characters that go to our school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another thing that&apos;s irritating me is the fact that I&apos;m now second-guessing my roommate pair. By second guessing, I mean me and someone else now want to room with each other instead of the originally agreed pairs. This wouldn&apos;t be a huge problem if we were, y&apos;know, fully dorming together, but now with the fact that they could possibly split our group by roommate pairs, I&apos;m worrying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another possibility I was thinking was, well, &lt;em&gt;what would happen if we literally run out of our own housing?&lt;/em&gt; The next possible options I&apos;d think the college would pursue is either renting out hotels or using the dorms of other Colleges of the Fenway schools. I&apos;d obviously much prefer the later due to it remaining in somewhat close proximity to campus, and it being a traditional dorm. As for a hotel, while it would be further away and we&apos;d lack the ability to customize our rooms, it does come through in some other cases such as room service and in-hotel restauraunts and such.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I honestly think this whole thing is just a symptom of overadmitting. My class, the Class of 2028, was the largest admitting class to date. If any future classes are bigger than mine, well... god help them I guess. Anyway, we have three halls that only Freshman can stay in, while the upperclassmen get three other halls that they can stay in for those whole 3 years. Since upperclassmen can stay in these dorms for so long, that obviously creates a space issue for rising upperclassmen. This should&apos;ve been taken into account when admissions were being done, but clearly it wasn&apos;t. &lt;em&gt;sigh&lt;/em&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded></item><item><title>A troublesome trip to Taco Bell</title><link>https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/1-22-2025/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/1-22-2025/</guid><description>I just wanted to go to Taco Bell to eat with my friends. Unfortunately, the T worked its magic and made that not so easy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Usually the T treats me pretty well. This was another night it unfortunately didn&apos;t.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, late at night (around 11 o&apos;clock) my friends wanted to go to Taco Bell, so I of course tagged along. I was pretty hungry as well, after all. The closest Taco Bell to our college dorm is about a 20-30 minute walk, so walking there usually isn&apos;t an issue but this time we decided to take the T due to how frigid it was outside. This Taco Bell is luckily quite easy to get to by transit as it&apos;s right across the street from Amory Street. Of course, the T made this much more difficult than it should&apos;ve been.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We got on at Museum of Fine Arts and everything was fine until we grinded to a halt at Symphony. We stood at the platform for around 15 minutes because of, guess what? A disabled train ahead of us. Numerous people got on and off in the time we were waiting, but we were determined to get Taco Bell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the train starting moving again we were excited as we thought this was the end of the delays. Turns out it wasn&apos;t. Things were smooth sailing until we got to the junction after Copley where the E branches off. We were just sitting here with no explanation until the conductor came onto the intercom saying that there was a power issue at Arlington. We didn&apos;t think much of it, since the last delay was only about 15 minutes, but this delay quickly spiraled into an &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOUR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. I was honestly getting ticked off because all we wanted was Taco Bell, yet our journey was turning into this long-winded nightmare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We were all rejoiced when we started moving again. We got off at Arlington to transfer westbound to the B. Me and two other friends were still enthusiastic about Taco Bell, buit the other two decided to split off from us here and go to the Taco Bell in Downtown Crossing which was indeed closer. We didn&apos;t think much of that until one of the friends I was still with was texted by one of the two that split off, saying the other was feeling sick- almost as if they were going to throw up- so they decided to just head back to our dorm. I honestly felt pretty bad for them because they had wasted immense time on this 1hr+ long journey for Taco Bell, only for it to end in them &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; getting Taco Bell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Me and my two other friends did end up getting to the Taco Bell with no other delays or funny business getting in our way. I got a Grilled Cheese Burrito modified to a point that I don&apos;t remember the specifics of, and we called an Uber to get back to the dorm because T service had ended and it was too damn cold out to walk.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded></item><item><title>My newfound appreciation for biking</title><link>https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/12-27-2024/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/12-27-2024/</guid><description>I have been scared to learn how to ride a bike for my whole life, until now. And honestly, I don&apos;t know what I was scared of. I&apos;m a natural at biking!</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Biking throughout my life&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Throughout my childhood, I did not have a good relationship with biking. My parents attempted to teach me numerous times when I was very young, but I could never get the damn fear of falling and hurting myself out of my head. My parents tried everything but nothing worked. There were only ever a few times I remember being able to get my bike going on my own for the most part. I think a large part of this was due to the fact of me being little; I just couldn&apos;t handle that fear and was unable to put it past me, so I would always clam up whenever my parents would try to give me instructions or help me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This inability to learn biking led me to the world of scooters. I very quickly adapted to scooters and became very good at riding them. My parents would come out with me all the time to watch me scooter around the block and such. A few years ago I even bought myself an electric scooter that I still have and use to this day. I think I was able to get the hang of scooters so quickly because they&apos;re easier to learn than bikes; you&apos;re standing, there&apos;s less to think about, and your center of gravity is higher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This all changed when I moved to Boston for college. I did not bring my electric scooter down with me because it would&apos;ve been way too bulky, nor would I have anywhere to store it down here. I was already aware of Boston&apos;s BlueBikes system, but I had never observed it on a day-to-day basis before. Seeing a ton of people riding them around the city and realizing how inconvenient many of my trips are by public transit, I realized I needed to get this fear out of my head and try learning how to ride a bike again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did some searching around and found the Bicycle Riding School, based in Somerville. After reading all the good feedback, I booked a private lesson with one of the teachers, Susan. I was not prepared for how well I would end up doing during this practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Susan, my teacher, was impressed almost right off the bat. I was not as clumsy with the bike as most first-timers are. I was able to get the hang of pushing off and trying to balance pretty quickly. Same thing with learning how to properly turn and bike in a straight line. When she added pedaling into the mix, I also had very little trouble getting the hang of it. The biggest problem I had was starting from a stop, as that would make my balance go totally out of wack. But by the time the lesson was over, Susan was impressed and told me I got the hang of biking unusually fast compared to her usual students.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, I told Susan this as well, but I suspect a reason I was able to get the hang of biking so quickly is because of my years spent with scooters. When you think about it, scooters work on the same basic principle as bikes: balance. If you can&apos;t balance, you&apos;ll either be very wobbly or it&apos;ll just tip over on you. Scooters are just much more forgiving than bikes. I think those skills were able to transfer over to biking, and since I already had a good hang of balance from the getgo, all of the other pieces just kind of naturally fell into place. A lot of beginners seem to have this problem with balance at first, which leads to them feeling like they don&apos;t have full control of the bike and messing up other actions such as pedaling or turning because they have trouble doing that in conjunction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Christmas 2024&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started desiring a bike of my own and did intense research. After a while, I discovered Retrospec and their wide range of bikes. They weren&apos;t my first choice originally, but after comparing many other brands, Retrospec quickly became my favorite option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Christmas, I got an extremely nice Retrospce bike, along with numerous accessories. I&apos;ve ridden it around a fair bit and so far it&apos;s been a really good bike. I do honestly wish I had an ebike instead, but (quality) ones are much more expensive than comparable non-ebikes. I also already have an electric scooter, so managing two kinds of electric transportation would probably be a bit much for me. I will probably upgrade one day, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For now, the Retrospec will serve my needs just fine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Present day&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have since become extremely good at biking and bike very frequently around Boston via the Blue Bikes. And of course, when I&apos;m home, that&apos;s when I ride my Retrospec. I&apos;m honestly really happy I&apos;ve finally learned how to bike because it has opened up a whole new world of mobility to me. It&apos;s made so many trips more convenient, and biking is also just fun to do. In Boston, I&apos;ve biked so many trips you could easily traverse by public transit just for the fun of it. If you haven&apos;t learned how to bike yet, I strongly urge you to.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded></item><item><title>The turbulent development of my blog</title><link>https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/10-29-2024/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/10-29-2024/</guid><description>tfw you wanna add a blog with advanced features you don&apos;t know how to code, so you use a whole ass SSG just for the blog and embed it into your already static site</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;You may have noticed this blog stands out from the rest of my site. Here&apos;s why.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From this website&apos;s beginning, I&apos;ve always wanted to implement a blog. A self-hosted one that wouldn&apos;t be dependent on other platforms like Blogger or Wordpress. I really enjoy writing, and I wanted a place like this where I could freely log my life events, devlogs, and other stuff. Not even for any audience, really- I don&apos;t care if nobody reads this. I&apos;m writing for myself, first and foremost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The only problem was that I had no fucking clue where to even start in terms of making it. I knew I couldn&apos;t have a separate page for each post as that would severely bloat my website and make going through the blog very slow. I also wanted advanced features like categories, tags, searching, and so on- all things I have absolutely no idea how to code. So, to sum things up...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My requirements/desires:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Categories and tags&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search functionality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Archive page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Posts use Markdown&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Initially, I thought about using Zonelets to make my blog, but my biggest problem with it was the fact that blog posts use HTML. Markdown is really great because you can write things in plain text and formatting is extremely simple! I did not feel like having to write all of my blog posts in HTML tags when the simplicity of Markdown exists. And so, the search continued...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My continued searching led me, ironically, to services like Wordpress. I could technically embed a Wordpress blog within my site... unfortunately, Wordpress isn&apos;t free (well, technically it can be, but the free tier was not what I was looking for), and I did not feel like self-hosting it. However, I kept this idea of embedding another site within mine in my head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, my search finally led me to static site generators! These generators are meant to be used to make whole websites with, such as portfolios, blogs, and much more. I realized I coould just use an SSG to create my blog, then embed its pages within the Blog page on my website. Perfect!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I spent a decent amount of time comparing different ones to each other until settling on &lt;a href=&quot;https://astro.build/&quot;&gt;Astro&lt;/a&gt;. I then went between a few different themes before settling on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/saicaca/fuwari&quot;&gt;Fuwari&lt;/a&gt;. This was a perfect solution for me. Fuwari not only looks really pleasing and has nice animations, but it came with categories, tags, an archive, searching, and much more (I&apos;ve very heavily modified it) all built in. And, best of all, posts are written Markdown!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;As you could probably guess, implementing this blog didn&apos;t go exactly smooth.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The relative link debacle&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Initially, I had this package called &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ixkaito/astro-relative-links&quot;&gt;Astro Relative Links&lt;/a&gt; integrated into the blog. This would generate all the links in the build as relative paths so I could use it through my &lt;em&gt;local files&lt;/em&gt; instead of the website. Unbeknownst to me, this was the root cause of numerous navigation errors when I&apos;d access the blog through my &lt;em&gt;website&lt;/em&gt; instead of the local files. The relative links made it so certain links would just append themselves onto the end of the current page&apos;s URL, leading to a page that doesn&apos;t exist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was stuck figuring out this problem for a while and had no clue why it was happening. I attempted countless fixes: changing Astro&apos;s base URL, changing the individual page URLs, changing destinations, among other things. None of it worked. Until one day, I decided to try disabling that package as it was the last link-related thing I could think of... and that fixed it. I kicked myself at how long it took me to figure out such a simple fix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The catastrophic .git fuckup&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Another time, I wanted to try Fuwari&apos;s draft feature. It ended in me having to delete my local files and start over.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, Fuwari has this cool feature where you can set posts as a draft. This makes it so the post doesn&apos;t show up on the site when you build it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had already wrapped up my work on the site for that day when I thought of experimenting with this on a post that I was still writing at the time. I had already committed and pushed that day&apos;s changes, so I changed the post into a draft then built the site and ammended the previous commit. What could go wrong?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was immediately met with a shitton of merge conflicts. I realized that perhaps ammending that commit instead of creating a new one was a bad idea so I tried aborting the commit somehow but I couldn&apos;t figure out any way to. I tried commands like &lt;code&gt;git reset&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;git merge --abort&lt;/code&gt; to no avail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, for some reason, I thought checking out the previous commit would somehow get me out of this situation. Not knowing how detached HEADs work, I thought this would allow me to pull that previous commit and reset the state of my local files. Since my HEAD was now detached, I soon found that to not be the case. I proceeded to frantically search up how to reconnect the HEAD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did end up reconnecting the HEAD. I also managed to pull that previous commit, which of course gave me more merge conflicts that I resolved this time. I&apos;m not sure if I completely reconnected the HEAD, though, because now I was getting credential errors every time I tried to sync the changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://files.catbox.moe/ccxyc2.png&quot; alt=&quot;Credential error in Visual Studio Code&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was where I realized the situation was just way too far gone and I nuked my local files so I could clone the GitHub repo and start over from the commit I tried to ammend. So, moral of the story? Only ammend simple, easily mergeable changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;In conclusion...&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I now have a really nice and fully functional blog on my site! I&apos;m really happy with it. Could I have found a way less convoluted than using a whole ass SSG just for my blog only to embed it on my already static site? Probably. But you know the saying... if it ain&apos;t broke, don&apos;t fix it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded></item><item><title>A troublesome trip to Target</title><link>https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/10-23-2024/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/10-23-2024/</guid><description>I just wanted to go to Target to get a slicker brush and some snacks. Unfortunately, the T worked its magic and made that not so easy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Usually the T treats me pretty well. This was one of the nights it unfortunately didn&apos;t.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So earlier today I had two errands I wanted to run. First, I needed to go Target to pick up a slicker brush for my new fursuit and some snacks. After, I wanted to stop at Primark to pick up some more skirts. Since I was going to the Target in Porter, I took the T as I usually do. Normally it&apos;s pretty uneventful, but today was a bit different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First I took the Green Line to Park Street to transfer to the Red Line, and then intended to take it to Porter. This is where things gets interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ride is normal until for seemingly no reason the operator slammed on the emergency brakes in the tunnel to Charles/MGH. This wasn&apos;t a one time thing- I&apos;m not sure why, but this kept happening between every single station. No announcements about it or anything. Nothing else of note happened until we got to Central, which was when the operator announced that my train was switching to an express to Alewife at Harvard because there were two trains bunched right behind us, and that if we were getting off at Porter or Davis (so including me, of course) then we&apos;d have to wait at Harvard for the next train.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, not one, but two more emergency stops later we made it to Harvard and I disembarked. The train left and the next one pulled in- only for them to announce that this train was now turning around back towards Boston! Seriously guys? So we had to wait like 7 more minutes until the next non-express train pulled in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Porter, I took the elevators of course. Ain&apos;t no way I&apos;m trekking up those long ass escalators or stairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, the way back was pretty uneventful. The train I took back wasn&apos;t doing the emergency stopping between stations so I have no clue what was up with that. One of my friends suggested police activity when I brought it up, but I never noticed anything awry happening at the stations...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, due to how... well, turbulent my trip to Target was, it took way longer than it should&apos;ve and I didn&apos;t have time to go to Primark after to get more skirts like I originally planned. But I can just stop by there tomorrow!&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded></item><item><title>Getting my fursuit</title><link>https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/10-18-2024/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/10-18-2024/</guid><description>$1200 and almost a year later, I have finally gotten my first fursuit. I have also fallen absolutely in love with it. Furry conventions, here we come!</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;The beginnings...&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I became a furry in mid-2022. That is when I bought my current VRChat avatar and commisioned a ref sheet based off of it. I had always wanted a fursuit since the beginning, but at the start I knew it would be a while until I could actually afford one, especially considering I was only 16 at the time and didn&apos;t exactly have a stable job or income yet...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fast forward to February of this year. Now that I had a stable job and income for a while at that point, I could finally afford a fursuit. I researched makers for quite a while and I was having a lot of difficulty finding local (US or Canada based) makers that offered good quality and an artstyle I liked at an affordable price. The fact that I didn&apos;t have an Instagram account at the time didn&apos;t help either, as a lot of makers I discovered in my search were &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; on Instagram, and you obviously can&apos;t DM people without an account.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My original rationale looking for local makers was that communication might be easier and shipping wouldn&apos;t take as long. But I just couldn&apos;t find any I liked, so I eventually expanded my search into foreign makers. This opened up a lot more options until I finally found a maker that matched my criteria: &lt;a href=&quot;https://silvenahandmade.com/&quot;&gt;Silvena Handmade&lt;/a&gt;. I loved her suit style, the suits looked high quality, and a full partial for my sona was only quoted at $1200!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Getting the fursuit made&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started off with a payment plan, as while I technically could&apos;ve afforded to pay the $1200 in full, I didn&apos;t feel comfortable doing that. It took me a few months to pay that off doing payments every other week. Only once I paid it off fully did she start working on the suit. It took another few months for the suit to be completed, but this timeline was nothing I didn&apos;t expect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was really nice throughout the whole process, from the quote to shipping. I would absolutely recommend her to anybody looking to buy a fursuit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The final result&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is what the fursuit ended up looking like in person! You can see a picture of me in it on my About Me page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://files.catbox.moe/d009vv.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A picture of all my fursuit&apos;s pieces. From left to right: the head, the two hand paws, the tail, and the arm sleeves.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were a couple nice surprises, such as the fur looking more vibrant than I expected. I also forgot to tell her what kind of jaw I wanted, so she gave me a movable jaw which is pretty sweet! I&apos;m also pursuing options for fursuit fans because it can get pretty toasty inside the head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What do I plan to do with it? Well, wear it of course. But I&apos;m also planning on attending my first ever furry convention, Anthro New England 2025, and I am extremely excited to bring Magmum along with me! In fact, conventions are one of the reasons I wanted a fursuit in the first place. Going to them without one is boring!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m also hoping to be able to attend Furcationland 2025, but that kinda hinges on whether or not I&apos;m able to afford the hotel + some extra for the dealers den and/or food when the time comes. The con&apos;s official hotels were way too expensive for me, so I managed to cop a reservation at the America&apos;s Best Value Inn in Scarborough, a 40-ish minute bus ride away from Portland, for only $79/night and $258 total. Conveniently, it has free cancelation until April 8th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, yeah... that is the journey of me getting my fursuit.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>