<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Vee&apos;s Domain</title><description>Blog</description><link>https://veesdomain.xyz/</link><language>en</language><item><title>The turbulent development of my blog</title><link>https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/10-29-2024/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/10-29-2024/</guid><description>tfw you wanna add a blog with advanced features you don&apos;t know how to code, so you use a whole ass SSG just for the blog and embed it into your already static site</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;You may have noticed this blog stands out from the rest of my site. Here&apos;s why.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From this website&apos;s beginning, I&apos;ve always wanted to implement a blog. A self-hosted one that wouldn&apos;t be dependent on other platforms like Blogger or Wordpress. I really enjoy writing, and I wanted a place like this where I could freely log my life events, devlogs, and other stuff. Not even for any audience, really- I don&apos;t care if nobody reads this. I&apos;m writing for myself, first and foremost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The only problem was that I had no fucking clue where to even start in terms of making it. I knew I couldn&apos;t have a separate page for each post as that would severely bloat my website and make going through the blog very slow. I also wanted advanced features like categories, tags, searching, and so on- all things I have absolutely no idea how to code. So, to sum things up...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My requirements/desires:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Categories and tags&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search functionality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Archive page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Posts use Markdown&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Initially, I thought about using Zonelets to make my blog, but my biggest problem with it was the fact that blog posts use HTML. Markdown is really great because you can write things in plain text and formatting is extremely simple! I did not feel like having to write all of my blog posts in HTML tags when the simplicity of Markdown exists. And so, the search continued...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My continued searching led me, ironically, to services like Wordpress. I could technically embed a Wordpress blog within my site... unfortunately, Wordpress isn&apos;t free (well, technically it can be, but the free tier was not what I was looking for), and I did not feel like self-hosting it. However, I kept this idea of embedding another site within mine in my head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, my search finally led me to static site generators! These generators are meant to be used to make whole websites with, such as portfolios, blogs, and much more. I realized I coould just use an SSG to create my blog, then embed its pages within the Blog page on my website. Perfect!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I spent a decent amount of time comparing different ones to each other until settling on &lt;a href=&quot;https://astro.build/&quot;&gt;Astro&lt;/a&gt;. I then went between a few different themes before settling on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/saicaca/fuwari&quot;&gt;Fuwari&lt;/a&gt;. This was a perfect solution for me. Fuwari not only looks really pleasing and has nice animations, but it came with categories, tags, an archive, searching, and much more (I&apos;ve very heavily modified it) all built in. And, best of all, posts are written Markdown!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;As you could probably guess, implementing this blog didn&apos;t go exactly smooth.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The relative link debacle&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Initially, I had this package called &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ixkaito/astro-relative-links&quot;&gt;Astro Relative Links&lt;/a&gt; integrated into the blog. This would generate all the links in the build as relative paths so I could use it through my &lt;em&gt;local files&lt;/em&gt; instead of the website. Unbeknownst to me, this was the root cause of numerous navigation errors when I&apos;d access the blog through my &lt;em&gt;website&lt;/em&gt; instead of the local files. The relative links made it so certain links would just append themselves onto the end of the current page&apos;s URL, leading to a page that doesn&apos;t exist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was stuck figuring out this problem for a while and had no clue why it was happening. I attempted countless fixes: changing Astro&apos;s base URL, changing the individual page URLs, changing destinations, among other things. None of it worked. Until one day, I decided to try disabling that package as it was the last link-related thing I could think of... and that fixed it. I kicked myself at how long it took me to figure out such a simple fix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The catastrophic .git fuckup&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Another time, I wanted to try Fuwari&apos;s draft feature. It ended in me having to delete my local files and start over.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, Fuwari has this cool feature where you can set posts as a draft. This makes it so the post doesn&apos;t show up on the site when you build it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had already wrapped up my work on the site for that day when I thought of experimenting with this on a post that I was still writing at the time. I had already committed and pushed that day&apos;s changes, so I changed the post into a draft then built the site and ammended the previous commit. What could go wrong?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was immediately met with a shitton of merge conflicts. I realized that perhaps ammending that commit instead of creating a new one was a bad idea so I tried aborting the commit somehow but I couldn&apos;t figure out any way to. I tried commands like &lt;code&gt;git reset&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;git merge --abort&lt;/code&gt; to no avail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, for some reason, I thought checking out the previous commit would somehow get me out of this situation. Not knowing how detached HEADs work, I thought this would allow me to pull that previous commit and reset the state of my local files. Since my HEAD was now detached, I soon found that to not be the case. I proceeded to frantically search up how to reconnect the HEAD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did end up reconnecting the HEAD. I also managed to pull that previous commit, which of course gave me more merge conflicts that I resolved this time. I&apos;m not sure if I completely reconnected the HEAD, though, because now I was getting credential errors every time I tried to sync the changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://files.catbox.moe/ccxyc2.png&quot; alt=&quot;Credential error in Visual Studio Code&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was where I realized the situation was just way too far gone and I nuked my local files so I could clone the GitHub repo and start over from the commit I tried to ammend. So, moral of the story? Only ammend simple, easily mergeable changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;In conclusion...&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I now have a really nice and fully functional blog on my site! I&apos;m really happy with it. Could I have found a way less convoluted than using a whole ass SSG just for my blog only to embed it on my already static site? Probably. But you know the saying... if it ain&apos;t broke, don&apos;t fix it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded></item><item><title>A troublesome trip to Target</title><link>https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/10-23-2024/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/10-23-2024/</guid><description>I just wanted to go to Target to get a slicker brush and some snacks. Unfortunately, the T worked its magic and made that not so easy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Usually the T treats me pretty well. This was one of the nights it unfortunately didn&apos;t.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So earlier today I had two errands I wanted to run. First, I needed to go Target to pick up a slicker brush for my new fursuit and some snacks. After, I wanted to stop at Primark to pick up some more skirts. Since I was going to the Target in Porter, I took the T as I usually do. Normally it&apos;s pretty uneventful, but today was a bit different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First I took the Green Line to Park Street to transfer to the Red Line, and then intended to take it to Porter. This is where things gets interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ride is normal until for seemingly no reason the operator slammed on the emergency brakes in the tunnel to Charles/MGH. This wasn&apos;t a one time thing- I&apos;m not sure why, but this kept happening between every single station. No announcements about it or anything. Nothing else of note happened until we got to Central, which was when the operator announced that my train was switching to an express to Alewife at Harvard because there were two trains bunched right behind us, and that if we were getting off at Porter or Davis (so including me, of course) then we&apos;d have to wait at Harvard for the next train.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, not one, but two more emergency stops later we made it to Harvard and I disembarked. The train left and the next one pulled in- only for them to announce that this train was now turning around back towards Boston! Seriously guys? So we had to wait like 7 more minutes until the next non-express train pulled in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Porter, I took the elevators of course. Ain&apos;t no way I&apos;m trekking up those long ass escalators or stairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, the way back was pretty uneventful. The train I took back wasn&apos;t doing the emergency stopping between stations so I have no clue what was up with that. One of my friends suggested police activity when I brought it up, but I never noticed anything awry happening at the stations...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, due to how... well, turbulent my trip to Target was, it took way longer than it should&apos;ve and I didn&apos;t have time to go to Primark after to get more skirts like I originally planned. But I can just stop by there tomorrow!&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded></item><item><title>Getting my fursuit</title><link>https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/10-18-2024/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://veesdomain.xyz/posts/10-18-2024/</guid><description>$1200 and almost a year later, I have finally gotten my first fursuit. I have also fallen absolutely in love with it. Furry conventions, here we come!</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;The beginnings...&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I became a furry in mid-2022. That is when I bought my current VRChat avatar and commisioned a ref sheet based off of it. I had always wanted a fursuit since the beginning, but at the start I knew it would be a while until I could actually afford one, especially considering I was only 16 at the time and didn&apos;t exactly have a stable job or income yet...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fast forward to February of this year. Now that I had a stable job and income for a while at that point, I could finally afford a fursuit. I researched makers for quite a while and I was having a lot of difficulty finding local (US or Canada based) makers that offered good quality and an artstyle I liked at an affordable price. The fact that I didn&apos;t have an Instagram account at the time didn&apos;t help either, as a lot of makers I discovered in my search were &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; on Instagram, and you obviously can&apos;t DM people without an account.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My original rationale looking for local makers was that communication might be easier and shipping wouldn&apos;t take as long. But I just couldn&apos;t find any I liked, so I eventually expanded my search into foreign makers. This opened up a lot more options until I finally found a maker that matched my criteria: &lt;a href=&quot;https://silvenahandmade.com/&quot;&gt;Silvena Handmade&lt;/a&gt;. I loved her suit style, the suits looked high quality, and a full partial for my sona was only quoted at $1200!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Getting the fursuit made&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started off with a payment plan, as while I technically could&apos;ve afforded to pay the $1200 in full, I didn&apos;t feel comfortable doing that. It took me a few months to pay that off doing payments every other week. Only once I paid it off fully did she start working on the suit. It took another few months for the suit to be completed, but this timeline was nothing I didn&apos;t expect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was really nice throughout the whole process, from the quote to shipping. I would absolutely recommend her to anybody looking to buy a fursuit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The final result&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is what the fursuit ended up looking like in person! You can see a picture of me in it on my About Me page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://files.catbox.moe/d009vv.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A picture of all my fursuit&apos;s pieces. From left to right: the head, the two hand paws, the tail, and the arm sleeves.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were a couple nice surprises, such as the fur looking more vibrant than I expected. I also forgot to tell her what kind of jaw I wanted, so she gave me a movable jaw which is pretty sweet! I&apos;m also pursuing options for fursuit fans because it can get pretty toasty inside the head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What do I plan to do with it? Well, wear it of course. But I&apos;m also planning on attending my first ever furry convention, Anthro New England 2025, and I am extremely excited to bring Magmum along with me! In fact, conventions are one of the reasons I wanted a fursuit in the first place. Going to them without one is boring!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m also hoping to be able to attend Furcationland 2025, but that kinda hinges on whether or not I&apos;m able to afford the hotel + some extra for the dealers den and/or food when the time comes. The con&apos;s official hotels were way too expensive for me, so I managed to cop a reservation at the America&apos;s Best Value Inn in Scarborough, a 40-ish minute bus ride away from Portland, for only $79/night and $258 total. Conveniently, it has free cancelation until April 8th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, yeah... that is the journey of me getting my fursuit.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>